Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- District Office Records, 1971-1994; Series VII
  - - Bellingham Issue Files, 1971-1994; Subseries 2
    - Native Americans
      - Swinomish Tribe, Aug-Dec 1994 (Box-folder 335/2)
    - Naval Air Station: Whidbey
      - Base Closure, 1990 (Box-folder 335/3)
      - Base Closure, Jan-Mar 1991 (Box-folder 335/4)
      - Base Closure, Apr 1991 (Box-folder 335/5)
      - Base Closure, May 1991 (Box-folder 335/6)
      - Base Closure, Jun-Aug 1991 (Box-folder 335/7)
      - Base Closure, Sep-Dec 1991 (Box-folder 335/8)
      - Base Closure, 1992 (Box-folder 335/9)
      - Base Closure, 1993 (Box-folder 335/10)
      - Base Closure, 1994 (Box-folder 335/11)
      - Jet Noise, 1986 (Box-folder 335/12)
      - Jet Noise, Jul 1987 (Box-folder 335/13)
      - Jet Noise, Aug 1987 (Box-folder 335/14)
      - Jet Noise, Sep 1987 (Box-folder 335/15)
      - Jet Noise, Oct 1987 (Box-folder 335/16)
      - Jet Noise, Nov 1987 (Box-folder 335/17)
      - Jet Noise, Dec 1987 (Box-folder 335/18)
      - Jet Noise, Jan 1988 (Box-folder 336/1)
      - Jet Noise, Feb 1988 (Box-folder 336/2)
      - Jet Noise, Mar 1988 (Box-folder 336/3)
      - Jet Noise, Apr 1988 (Box-folder 336/4)
      - Jet Noise, May 1988 (Box-folder 336/5)
      - Jet Noise, Jun 1988 (Box-folder 336/6)
      - Jet Noise, Jul 1988 (Box-folder 336/7)
      - Jet Noise, Aug 1988 (Box-folder 336/8)
      - Jet Noise, Sep 1988 (Box-folder 336/9)
      - Jet Noise, Oct-Dec 1988 (Box-folder 336/10)
      - Jet Noise, Jan-Feb 1989 (Box-folder 336/11)
      - Jet Noise, Mar 1989 (Box-folder 336/12)
      - Jet Noise, Apr-May 1989 (Box-folder 336/13)
      - Jet Noise, Jun-Aug 1989 (Box-folder 336/14)
      - Jet Noise, Sep-Dec 1989 (Box-folder 336/15)
      - Jet Noise, 1990 (Box-folder 336/16)
      - Jet Noise, 1991 (Box-folder 336/17)
      - Jet Noise, 1992 (Box-folder 337/1)
      - Jet Noise, 1993 (Box-folder 337/2)
      - Jet Noise, 1994 (Box-folder 337/3)
      - Jet Noise: Guemes Island, 1989-90 (Box-folder 337/4)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration
      - San Juan Islands Sanctuary, 1988-89 (Box-folder 337/5)
      - San Juan Islands Sanctuary, 1991-94 (Box-folder 337/6)
    - Olga, Washington
      - Post Office, 1986 (Box-folder 337/7)
    - Pea Cyst Nemotode
      - Issues, 1993-94 (Box-folder 337/8)
    - Point Roberts, Washington
      - Water Supply, 1983-85 (Box-folder 337/9)
      - Water Supply, 1986-88 (Box-folder 337/10)
    - Redistricting
      - Issues: Pre-1979, pre-1979 (Box-folder 337/11)
      - Issues, 1979 (Box-folder 337/12)
      - Issues, 1980 (Box-folder 337/13)
      - Issues, 1981 (Box-folder 337/14)
      - Issues, 1982 (Box-folder 337/15)
      - Issues, 1983 (Box-folder 337/16)
      - Maps, 1979-83 (Box-folder 337/17)
    - Regional Power Plan
      - Bill, 1979 (Box-folder 338/1)
      - Bill, Jan-Feb 1980 (Box-folder 338/2)
      - Bill, Mar 1980 (Box-folder 338/3)
      - Bill, Apr-Aug 1980 (Box-folder 338/4)
      - Bill, Sep 1980 (Box-folder 338/5)
      - Bill, Oct-Dec 1980 (Box-folder 338/6)
      - Bill: 1980 (Undated), 1980 (Box-folder 338/7)
      - Bill, 1981 (Box-folder 338/8)
      - Plan, 1977-78 (Box-folder 338/9)
      - Plan, 1979 (Box-folder 338/10)
      - Plan, 1980 (Box-folder 338/11)
      - Plan, 1981 (Box-folder 338/12)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act
      - Bill, 1991-92 (Box-folder 338/13)
    - Safe Drinking Water Act
      - Bill, 1988 (Box-folder 338/14)
      - Bill, 1991 (Box-folder 339/1)
      - Bill, 1992 (Box-folder 339/2)
      - Bill, 1993 (Box-folder 339/3)
      - Bill, 1994 (Box-folder 339/4)
    - Sewage
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, Jan-Feb 1986 (Box-folder 339/5)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, Mar 1986 (Box-folder 339/6)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, Apr-Jul 1986 (Box-folder 339/7)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, Aug-Oct 1986 (Box-folder 339/8)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, Nov-Dec 1986 (Box-folder 339/9)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, 1987 (Box-folder 339/10)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, 1988 (Box-folder 339/11)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, 1989 (Box-folder 339/12)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, 1990 (Box-folder 339/13)
      - Secondary Sewage Treatment, 1991 (Box-folder 339/14)
    - Strawberries
      - Child Labor, 1977 (Box-folder 339/15)
      - Child Labor, 1978-79 (Box-folder 339/16)
      - Child Labor, 1980-81 (Box-folder 339/17)
      - Child Labor: Hearing Report, 1981 (Box-folder 339/18)
    - Timber Industry
      - Issues, 1985 (Box-folder 339/19)
      - Issues, Jan-May 1986 (Box-folder 339/20)
      - Issues, Jun-Sep 1986 (Box-folder 339/21)
      - Issues, Oct-Dec 1986 (Box-folder 339/22)
      - Issues, 1987 (Box-folder 339/23)
      - Issues, Jan-May 1988 (Box-folder 340/1)
      - Issues, Jun-Dec 1988 (Box-folder 340/2)
    - U.S. Forest Service
      - Issues, 1985 (Box-folder 340/3)
      - Issues, Jan 1986 (Box-folder 340/4)
      - Issues, Feb 1986 (Box-folder 340/5)
      - Issues, Mar-Jul 1986 (Box-folder 340/6)
      - Issues, Aug 1986 (Box-folder 340/7)
      - Issues, Sep-Dec 1986 (Box-folder 340/8)
      - Issues: Reports, 1986 (Box-folder 340/9)
      - Issues, Jan 1987 (Box-folder 340/10)
      - Issues, Feb-Apr 1987 (Box-folder 340/11)
      - Issues, May-Aug 1987 (Box-folder 340/12)
      - Issues, Sep-Dec 1987 (Box-folder 340/13)
      - Issues, Dec 1987 (Box-folder 340/14)
      - Issues: Reports, 1987 (Box-folder 340/15)
      - Issues, Jan 1988 (Box-folder 340/16)
      - Issues, Feb-Apr 1988 (Box-folder 340/17)
      - Issues, May-Jul 1988 (Box-folder 341/1)
      - Issues, Aug-Sep 1988 (Box-folder 341/2)
      - Issues, Oct-Dec 1988 (Box-folder 341/3)
      - Issues: Reports Part 1, 1988 (Box-folder 341/4)
      - Issues: Reports Part 2, 1988 (Box-folder 341/5)
      - Issues, Jan 1989 (Box-folder 341/6)
      - Issues, Feb 1989 (Box-folder 341/7)
      - Issues, Mar 1989 (Box-folder 341/8)
      - Issues, Apr 1989 (Box-folder 341/9)
      - Issues, May 1989 (Box-folder 341/10)
      - Issues, Jun 1989 (Box-folder 341/11)
      - Issues, Jul 1989 (Box-folder 341/12)
      - Issues, Aug 1989 (Box-folder 341/13)
      - Issues, Sep 1989 (Box-folder 341/14)
      - Issues, Oct 1989 (Box-folder 342/1)
      - Issues, Nov 1989 (Box-folder 342/2)
      - Issues, Dec 1989 (Box-folder 342/3)
      - Issues: Reports, 1989 (Box-folder 342/4)
      - Issues, Jan-Mar 1990 (Box-folder 342/5)
      - Issues, Apr 1990 (Box-folder 342/6)
      - Issues, May 1990 (Box-folder 342/7)
      - Issues, Jun-Dec 1990 (Box-folder 342/8)
      - Issues: Reports, 1990 (Box-folder 342/9)
      - Issues, 1991 (Box-folder 342/10)
      - Issues: Reports, 1991 (Box-folder 342/11)
      - Issues, 1992 (Box-folder 342/12)
      - Issues: Reports, 1992 (Box-folder 342/13)
      - Issues, 1993 (Box-folder 342/14)
      - Issues, 1994 (Box-folder 342/15)
      - Army Reserve Helicopter Training Permit, 1988-89 (Box-folder 342/16)
      - Campground Closures, 1984 (Box-folder 342/17)
      - Campground Closures, Jan-Apr 1985 (Box-folder 342/18)
      - Campground Closures, May 1985 (Box-folder 342/19)
      - Campground Closures, Jun-Jul 1985 (Box-folder 342/20)
      - Campground Closures, Aug-Dec 1985 (Box-folder 343/1)
      - Campground Closures, 1986 (Box-folder 343/2)
      - Campground Closures, 1987 (Box-folder 343/3)
    - Veteran's Center
      - Bellingham, 1993-94 (Box-folder 343/4)
    - Wetlands
      - Issues, 1989 (Box-folder 343/5)
      - Issues, 1990 (Box-folder 343/6)
      - Issues, 1991-93 (Box-folder 343/7)
    - Wild and Scenic Rivers
      - Issues, 1977 (Box-folder 343/8)
      - Issues, 1978 (Box-folder 343/9)
      - Issues, 1983 (Box-folder 343/10)
      - Issues, 1984 (Box-folder 343/11)
      - Issues, 1988-90 (Box-folder 343/12)
      - Issues, 1991 (Box-folder 343/13)
      - Issues, 1992 (Box-folder 343/14)
      - Issues, 1993-94 (Box-folder 343/15)
  - Everett District Office Files, 1978-1994; Subseries 3
    - Academy Review Process Parts 1-4, 1991-94 (Box-folder 344/1)
    - Academy Review Process Parts 5-12, 1991-94 (Box-folder 344/2)
    - Articles, 1984 (Box-folder 344/3)
    - Articles, 1986 (Box-folder 344/4)
    - Articles, 1987 (Box-folder 344/5)
    - Articles, 1988 (Box-folder 344/6)
    - Articles, 1989 (Box-folder 344/7)
    - Articles, 1990 (Box-folder 344/8)
    - Articles, 1991 (Box-folder 344/9)
    - Articles, 1992 (Box-folder 345/1)
    - Articles, 1993 (Box-folder 345/2)
    - Articles, 1994 (Box-folder 345/3)
    - Arts Contest, 1983 (Box-folder 345/4)
    - Arts Contest, 1984 (Box-folder 345/5)
    - Arts Contest, 1985 (Box-folder 345/6)
    - Arts Contest, 1986 (Box-folder 345/7)
    - Arts Contest, 1987 (Box-folder 345/8)
    - Arts Contest, 1988 (Box-folder 345/9)
    - Arts Contest, 1989 (Box-folder 345/10)
    - Bills, 1981 (Box-folder 345/11)
    - Biography, 1980-94 (Box-folder 345/12)
    - Conference: Economic Alternatives, 1980 (Box-folder 345/13)
    - Conference: Phoenix Group--Democratic Reconstruction, 1981 (Box-folder 345/14)
    - Conference: Economic Growth, 1986 (Box-folder 345/15)
    - Conference: U.S./Canada Trade, 1987 (Box-folder 346/1)
    - Conference: Housing, 1990 (Box-folder 346/2)
    - Conference: Housing, 1991 (Box-folder 346/3)
    - Correspondence: Incoming, 1979 (Box-folder 346/4)
    - Correspondence: Incoming, 1980 (Box-folder 346/5)
    - Correspondence: Incoming, 1981 (Box-folder 346/6)
    - Correspondence: Incoming, 1982 (Box-folder 346/7)
    - Correspondence: Incoming, 1983 (Box-folder 346/8)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jan-Jun 1979 (Box-folder 346/9)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul-Dec 1979 (Box-folder 346/10)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1980 (Box-folder 346/11)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jan 1981 (Box-folder 346/12)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Feb 1981 (Box-folder 346/13)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Mar 1981 (Box-folder 346/14)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Apr 1981 (Box-folder 346/15)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1981 (Box-folder 346/16)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1981 (Box-folder 346/17)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1981 (Box-folder 346/18)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1981 (Box-folder 346/19)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Sep 1981 (Box-folder 346/20)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Oct 1981 (Box-folder 346/21)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1981 (Box-folder 346/22)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Dec 1981 (Box-folder 346/23)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing --Lists, 1981 (Box-folder 346/24)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jan 1982 (Box-folder 346/25)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Feb 1982 (Box-folder 346/26)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Apr 1982 (Box-folder 346/27)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1982 (Box-folder 346/28)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1982 (Box-folder 346/29)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1982 (Box-folder 347/1)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1982 (Box-folder 347/2)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing Part 1, Oct 1982 (Box-folder 347/3)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing Part 2, Oct 1982 (Box-folder 347/4)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1982 (Box-folder 347/5)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jan 1983 (Box-folder 347/6)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Mar 1983 (Box-folder 347/7)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Apr 1983 (Box-folder 347/8)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1983 (Box-folder 347/9)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1983 (Box-folder 347/10)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1983 (Box-folder 347/11)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1983 (Box-folder 347/12)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Sep 1983 (Box-folder 347/13)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Oct 1983 (Box-folder 347/14)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1983 (Box-folder 347/15)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Dec 1983 (Box-folder 347/16)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jan 1984 (Box-folder 347/17)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Feb 1984 (Box-folder 347/18)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Mar 1984 (Box-folder 347/19)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Apr 1984 (Box-folder 347/20)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1984 (Box-folder 347/21)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1984 (Box-folder 347/22)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1984 (Box-folder 347/23)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1984 (Box-folder 347/24)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Sep 1984 (Box-folder 347/25)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Oct 1984 (Box-folder 347/26)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1984 (Box-folder 347/27)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, Dec 1984 (Box-folder 347/28)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing, 1985 (Box-folder 347/29)
    - Correspondence: Christmas Cards, 1979-94 (Box-folder 347/30)
    - Correspondence: "Greetings File", 1988-94 (Box-folder 347/31)
    - Correspondence: Invitations, 1979-81 (Box-folder 347/32)
    - Correspondence: Letters of Congratulation, 1978 (Box-folder 347/33)
    - Correspondence: Letters of Congratulation, 1979 (Box-folder 347/34)
    - Correspondence: Letters of Congratulation, 1980 (Box-folder 348/1)
    - Correspondence: "Nice Things About Al", Undated (Box-folder 348/2)
    - Correspondence: "Thank You" Letters, 1986-94 (Box-folder 348/3)
    - Forum: Health Care, 3/25/1985 (Box-folder 348/4)
    - Forum: Health Care, 9/26/1987 (Box-folder 348/5)
    - Forum: Health Care, 5/29/1990 (Box-folder 348/6)
    - Forum: Health Care, 2/11/1992 (Box-folder 348/7)
    - Grant Applications, 1979-80 (Box-folder 348/8)
    - Hearing: Presidential Primary--Seattle, WA, 1981 (Box-folder 348/9)
    - Hearing: Telephone--Everett, WA, 1983 (Box-folder 348/10)
    - Listening Post, 1979 (Box-folder 348/11)
    - Listening Post, 1980 (Box-folder 348/12)
    - Listening Post, 1981 (Box-folder 348/13)
    - Listening Post, 1982 (Box-folder 348/14)
    - Listening Post: Locations, Undated (Box-folder 348/15)
    - Memoranda: Staff, 1979-80 (Box-folder 348/16)
    - Newsletters, 1979-82 (Box-folder 348/17)
    - Newsletters, 1983-86 (Box-folder 348/18)
    - Newsletters, 1987-91 (Box-folder 348/19)
    - Press Releases, 1979 (Box-folder 349/1)
    - Press Releases, 1980 (Box-folder 349/2)
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box-folder 349/3)
    - Press Releases, 1983 (Box-folder 349/4)
    - Schedules, 1979 (Box-folder 349/5)
    - Schedules, 1980 (Box-folder 349/6)
    - Schedules, 1981 (Box-folder 349/7)
    - Schedules, Jan-Apr 1982 (Box-folder 349/8)
    - Schedules, May-Sep 1982 (Box-folder 349/9)
    - Schedules, Oct 1982 (Box-folder 349/10)
    - Schedules, 1986 (Box-folder 349/11)
    - Schedules, 1987 (Box-folder 349/12)
    - Schedules, 1988 (Box-folder 349/13)
    - Schedules, 1989 (Box-folder 350/1)
    - Schedules, 1990 (Box-folder 350/2)
    - Schedules, 1991 (Box-folder 350/3)
    - Schedules, 1992 (Box-folder 350/4)
    - Schedules, 1993 (Box-folder 350/5)
    - Schedules, 1994 (Box-folder 350/6)
    - Schedules: Misc., 1979-80 (Box-folder 350/7)
    - Senator Henry Jackson Memorial Service, 9/6/1983 (Box-folder 350/8)
    - Speeches, 1979 (Box-folder 350/9)
    - Speeches, 1980 (Box-folder 350/10)
    - Speeches, 1981 (Box-folder 350/11)
    - Speeches, 1982 (Box-folder 351/1)
    - Speeches, 1983 (Box-folder 351/2)
    - Speeches, 1984 (Box-folder 351/3)
    - Trip: 1, Jan 1979 (Box-folder 351/4)
    - Trip: 2, Feb 1979 (Box-folder 351/5)
    - Trip: 3, 3/17/1979 (Box-folder 351/6)
    - Trip: 4, 3/24/1979 (Box-folder 351/7)
    - Trip: 5, 4/12/1979 (Box-folder 351/8)
    - Trip: Pfizer Invitation, 4/16/1979 (Box-folder 351/9)
    - Trip: 6, 5/17/1979 (Box-folder 351/10)
    - Trip: Small Cities Seminar--Renton, WA, 4/21/1979 (Box-folder 351/11)
    - Trip: 7, 6/1/1979 (Box-folder 351/12)
    - Trip: 8, 7/2/1979 (Box-folder 351/13)
    - Trip: Retreat--Coupville, WA, 8/3/1979 (Box-folder 351/14)
    - Trip: 9/10, 8/3/79 to 9/5/79 (Box-folder 351/15)
    - Trip: 10, 1/15/1979 (Box-folder 352/1)
    - Trip: 11, 10/1/1979 (Box-folder 352/2)
    - Trip: 12, Nov 1979 (Box-folder 352/3)
    - Trip: 13, Dec 1979 (Box-folder 352/4)
    - Trip: 14, 12/7/1979 (Box-folder 352/5)
    - Trip: 1, Jan 1980 (Box-folder 352/6)
    - Trip: 2, Jan 1980 (Box-folder 352/7)
    - Trip, Feb 1980 (Box-folder 352/8)
    - Trip: 17, 3/21/1980 (Box-folder 352/9)
    - Trip, 4/4/1980 (Box-folder 352/10)
    - Trip: Community Conventions, 4/12/1980 (Box-folder 352/11)
    - Trip, 4/18/1980 (Box-folder 352/12)
    - Trip: 20, May 1980 (Box-folder 352/13)
    - Trip, 6/12/1980 (Box-folder 352/14)
    - Trip, 6/20/1980 (Box-folder 352/15)
    - Trip, Jul 1980 (Box-folder 352/16)
    - Trip, Aug 1980 (Box-folder 353/1)
    - Trip: 25, 8/28/1980 (Box-folder 353/2)
    - Trip, Sep 1980 (Box-folder 353/3)
    - Trip: 26, 9/13/1980 (Box-folder 353/4)
    - Trip: 28, 10/3/1980-11/8/1980 (Box-folder 353/5)
    - Trip: 1, 1/23/1981 (Box-folder 353/6)
    - Trip: 2, 2/11/1981 (Box-folder 353/7)
    - Trip: North Puget Sound Health Council, 2/24/1981 (Box-folder 353/8)
    - Trip, 3/19/1981 (Box-folder 353/9)
    - Trip, 4/20/1981 (Box-folder 353/10)
    - Trip, 5/21/1981 (Box-folder 353/11)
    - Trip, 6/6/1981 (Box-folder 353/12)
    - Trip, 6/26/1981 (Box-folder 353/13)
    - Trip, 8/1/1981-9/4/1981 (Box-folder 353/14)
    - Trip, 9/25/1981 (Box-folder 353/15)
    - Trip, 10/7/1981 (Box-folder 353/16)
    - Trip, 10/29/1981 (Box-folder 353/17)
    - Trip: Cancelled, 11/20/1981 (Box-folder 353/18)
    - Trip, 11/29/1981 (Box-folder 353/19)
    - Trip, 12/17/1981 (Box-folder 353/20)
    - Trip, 9/13/1984 (Box-folder 353/21)
    - Voting Record, 1983 (Box-folder 353/22)
  - Everett Issue Files, 1978-1994; Subseries 4
    - 88th Street Interchange, 1989-94 (Box-folder 354/1)
    - Arlington Airport, 1980 (Box-folder 354/2)
    - A.T.and T., 1982 (Box-folder 354/3)
    - Aviation: C5 and 747s, 1982 (Box-folder 354/4)
    - Boulder River, 1979-81 (Box-folder 354/5)
    - Bonneville Power Administration, 1982 (Box-folder 354/6)
    - Budget Cuts: Proposed by President Reagan, 1981 (Box-folder 354/7)
    - City of Sumas, 1979 (Box-folder 354/8)
    - Clean Air and Toxic Dumping, 1982 (Box-folder 354/9)
    - Community Transit: SCPTBA, 1980 (Box-folder 354/10)
    - Cross Ownership: (H.R.6228), 1979-80 (Box-folder 354/11)
    - Dalton, Howard: (H.R.3635), 1979-81 (Box-folder 354/12)
    - Democratic Party of Washington State, Undated (Box-folder 354/13)
    - E.A. Nord Company, 1979-80 (Box-folder 354/14)
    - Early Election Results, 1979-82 (Box-folder 354/15)
    - Ebey's Landing, 1979 (Box-folder 354/16)
    - Ebey's Landing, 1980 (Box-folder 354/17)
    - Ebey's Landing: Reports, 1980 (Box-folder 355/1)
    - Ebey's Landing, 1981 (Box-folder 355/2)
    - Ebey Slough Trestle, 1984-89 (Box-folder 355/3)
    - Ebey Slough Trestle, 1990 (Box-folder 355/4)
    - Ebey Slough Trestle, 1991-94 (Box-folder 355/5)
    - Energy Issues, 1980 (Box-folder 355/6)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1983 (Box-folder 355/7)
    - Everett Community College, 1981 (Box-folder 355/8)
    - Fishing Issues, 1979-80 (Box-folder 355/9)
    - Flood: Index, Sultan, etc., 1981 (Box-folder 355/10)
    - Farmers Home Administration: Prepayments, 1986-94 (Box-folder 355/11)
    - Federal Trade Comission: Used Cars, Undated (Box-folder 355/12)
    - F.U.S.E.: Irate Ratepayers Revolt, 1982 (Box-folder 355/13)
    - Gramm/Rudman Deficit Reduction, 1986 (Box-folder 355/14)
    - Granite Falls: Arsnic, 1988 (Box-folder 355/15)
    - Government Services Administration, 1982-85 (Box-folder 355/16)
    - Helium Energy Act, 1980 (Box-folder 355/17)
    - Hewlett-Packard, 1980-81 (Box-folder 355/18)
    - Home Incentive, 1980 (Box-folder 355/19)
    - Homeport: Everett, Apr 1985-May 1986 (Box-folder 356/1)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jun 1986 (Box-folder 356/2)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jul-Sep 1986 (Box-folder 356/3)
    - Homeport: Everett, Oct-Dec 1986 (Box-folder 356/4)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jan-Feb 1987 (Box-folder 356/5)
    - Homeport: Everett, Mar 1987 (Box-folder 356/6)
    - Homeport: Everett, Apr-Dec 1987 (Box-folder 356/7)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jan-Feb 1988 (Box-folder 356/8)
    - Homeport: Everett, Mar-May 1988 (Box-folder 356/9)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jun-Dec 1988 (Box-folder 356/10)
    - Homeport: Everett, 1989 (Box-folder 356/11)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jan-Mar 1990 (Box-folder 356/12)
    - Homeport: Everett, Apr-Dec 1990 (Box-folder 356/13)
    - Homeport: Everett, 1991-92 (Box-folder 356/14)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jan-May 1993 (Box-folder 356/15)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jun-Dec 1993 (Box-folder 356/16)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jan-Jun 1994 (Box-folder 357/1)
    - Homeport: Everett, Jul-Dec 1994 (Box-folder 357/2)
    - Housing Projects: Examples, 1992-93 (Box-folder 357/3)
    - Index: 2, 4D, 1980 (Box-folder 357/4)
    - Index Bridge, 1979 (Box-folder 357/5)
    - LaConner, 1979 (Box-folder 357/6)
    - Log Exports, 1979-80 (Box-folder 357/7)
    - Lynnwood: Sewer, 1978-80 (Box-folder 357/8)
    - Magnuson, Warren, 1980-81 (Box-folder 357/9)
    - Marriage Tax, 1980 (Box-folder 357/10)
    - Microsoft, 1993 (Box-folder 357/11)
    - Moral Majority, 1980-81 (Box-folder 357/12)
    - Native Americans: Fishing Rights, 1979 (Box-folder 357/13)
    - Norman Architectural Design, 1979-80 (Box-folder 357/14)
    - Northern Tier, 1979-82 (Box-folder 357/15)
    - Northwest Regional Power Act (NWRPA), 1978 (Box-folder 357/16)
    - NWRPA, Jan-Jul 1979 (Box-folder 357/17)
    - NWRPA, Aug 1979 (Box-folder 357/18)
    - NWRPA, Sep-Oct 1979 (Box-folder 357/19)
    - NWRPA, Nov 1979-Jan 1980 (Box-folder 357/20)
    - NWRPA, Feb 1980 (Box-folder 358/1)
    - NWRPA, Mar 1980 (Box-folder 358/2)
    - NWRPA, Apr-Dec 1980 (Box-folder 358/3)
    - NWRPA, 1981 (Box-folder 358/4)
    - NWRPA, 1982 (Box-folder 358/5)
    - Nuclear Waste Policy Act, 1982 (Box-folder 358/6)
    - Open Democratic Convention, 1980 (Box-folder 358/7)
    - Padilla Bay Estuary, 1979-82 (Box-folder 358/8)
    - Passage Foundation, 1979 (Box-folder 358/9)
    - Post Office: Langley, 1992-93 (Box-folder 358/10)
    - Presidential Primaries, 1980 (Box-folder 358/11)
    - "Project-Hispanic", 1979-81 (Box-folder 358/12)
    - Retarded Citizens: Institutionalization, 1978-79 (Box-folder 358/13)
    - Redistricting, Dec 1982 (Box-folder 358/14)
    - Redistricting: Census, 1979 (Box-folder 358/15)
    - Redistricting: Census Information Kit, 1980 (Box-folder 358/16)
    - Redistricting: Census Information Kit, 1982 (Box-folder 359/1)
    - Redistricting: Everett, 1982 (Box-folder 359/2)
    - Redistricting: Everett Lawsuit, 1982 (Box-folder 359/3)
    - Redistricting: Snohomish County Elections, 1980 (Box-folder 359/4)
    - Redistricting: Snohomish County, 1981 (Box-folder 359/5)
    - Redistricting: Washington State--Bill 3655, 1981 (Box-folder 359/6)
    - Redistricting: Washington State, 1982 (Box-folder 359/7)
    - Sauk River Flood: Darrington, 1980-81 (Box-folder 359/8)
    - Skagit Valley Nuclear Power: Proposed, 1980-81 (Box-folder 359/9)
    - Sky Valley Telephone Committee, 1979 (Box-folder 359/10)
    - Snohomish Basin Coordination Council, 1979-81 (Box-folder 359/11)
    - Snoqualmie Airport, 1980-81 (Box-folder 359/12)
    - Son Cedar Products, Inc., 1980 (Box-folder 360/1)
    - Stanley, Owen, 1979 (Box-folder 360/2)
    - Stanwood Flood Control, 1978-80 (Box-folder 360/3)
    - Starr, Richard: materials regarding kidnapping, ransom negotiations, eventual return, and subsequent death, 1977-1983, 1977-1983